

CHANDRA RAMDHAN PURNAMA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

"I am not a visionary. I'm an engineer. I'm happy with the people who are wandering around looking at the stars but I am looking at the ground and I want to fix the pothole before I fall in" - Linus Torvalds

CONTACT

- (+62) 838-2189-6126
- euclife@outlook.co.id
- in chandraramdhan
- https://euclife.github.io/
- 33 Manglid Street Bandung, Indonesia

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE —

PHP
JAVA
C++
C#
C
JAVA SCRIPT
GO

PYTHON

OTHER LANGUAGE

HTML

XML

CSS

SQL

INDONESIAN

ENGLISH

PROGAMMING FRAMEWORK -

LARAVEL
WORDPRESS
OCTOBER CMS
NODE JS
EXPRESS JS
DJANGO
ASP.NET

OTHER SKILLS

COREL DRAW

MS. OFFICE

JQUERY

BOOTSTRAP

PERSONAL INFORMATIONS

Courteous and enthusiastic person, I am interested in IT and everything in its orbit. I recently began to be fascinated by web programming, e.g developing apps and building websites. Currently focused on learning PHP but exposed in all aspects of web development including front and back end as well. Involved in IT-based project around 2 years for several organizations and wide range company, also have experiences on cloud computing platform such as AWS and Google Cloud Platform and having the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. INTERSOLUSI TEKNOLOGI ASIA (BTS.ID) JUNIOR DEVELOPER

12 AUG 2019 - NOW

- Build web applications and features
- Deployment apps into server
- Do some research and experiment for new technology

SRI BADUGA MUSEUM

INTERNSHIP

10 NOV 2018 - 14 MAR 2019

- Build web applications and features
- Deployment apps into server

STMIK & POLITEKNIK LPKIA CO-ASSISTANT PROFESSOR

2017

Assisting lecturers in teaching and learning activities

EDUCATION

STMIK & POLITEKNIK LPKIA

Associate's Degree of Informatics Engineering

2016 - 2019

Informatics Engineering

14 BANDUNG PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOL

HIGH SCHOOL

2013 - 2016

Science Major

HOBBIES







